<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interfaces on Velocitas</title>
    <link>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interfaces on Velocitas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 10:15:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Signal Interface</title>
      <link>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/vehicle_signal_interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/vehicle_signal_interface/</guid>
      <description>Providing CLI package Interface type-key devenv-devcontainer-setup vehicle-signal-interface The Vehicle Signal Interface formerly known as Vehicle Model interface type creates an interface to a signal interface described by the VSS spec. This interface will generate a source code package equivalent to the contents of your VSS JSON automatically upon devContainer creation.&#xA;If a Vehicle App requires a vehicle-signal-interface, it will act as a consumer of datapoints already available in the system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gRPC Service Interface</title>
      <link>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/grpc_interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/grpc_interface/</guid>
      <description>Providing CLI package Interface type-key devenv-devcontainer-setup grpc-interface Description This interface type introduces a dependency to a gRPC service. It is used to generate either client stubs (in case your application requires the interface) or server stubs (in case your application provides the interface). The result of the generation is a language specific and package manager specific source code package, integrated with the Velocitas SDK core.&#xA;If a Vehicle App requires a grpc-interface - a client stub embedded into the Velocitas framework will be generated and added as a build-time dependency of your application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publish Subscribe</title>
      <link>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/pubsub/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/velocitas/docs/concepts/development_model/vehicle_app_manifest/interfaces/pubsub/</guid>
      <description>Providing CLI package Interface type-key devenv-runtimes pubsub Description This interface type introduces a dependency to a publish and subscribe middleware. While this may change in the future due to new middlewares being adopted, at the moment this will always indicate a dependency to MQTT.&#xA;If a Vehicle App requires pubsub - this will influence the generated deployment specs to include a publish and subscribe broker (i.e. an MQTT broker).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
